The body should not be divided over
vaccines or over race. There is nothing
that should divide the body of Christ.
And you can almost see the hypocrisy
when a when a call was made last year to
divide the body because of religious
liberty and vaccines. There were people
who were because the church is an
apostasy anyway. The church is not the
church is the church is is it's no
longer the voice of of God on earth. and
and and there's corruption and and and
there were these ju just hey it what's
the big deal whole conferences are going
to fall and last year when I said hey no
no no no no wrong move you don't know
what you're talking about and now now in
in in light of certain events have taken
place over the last several weeks where
you now have this issue of race being
brought up in the church and questions
and talk of you know should we divide
should we have you know a black
conference or white conference. I say
no, that's still not the answer. I mean,
wow, what a what a slip up. Black
conferences and white conferences. I'll
get to that in a moment. Should we
separate based on on this? And I'm
saying no. The same people who were
cheering back then and saying, "Oh, this
is boldness. This is courage. We need to
stand." Are saying, "Well, how can you?
This is this is divisive. And this is a"
And you know what? Trust me. Trust me.
Guess what's going to happen? Those who
follow right Jesus are going to be like,
"Well, you see the difference between
that and this is." And those who follow
left Jesus who are cheering this on will
say, "Well, the difference between this
and that was," and I'm telling you,
telling you you guys, dividing the body
is never the answer. That's what Satan
wants to do. Last year when people were
talking about we need to boycott the GC
and and we're going to take our tithe
and divert it and people were cheering
it and I said, "No, that's wrong. We we
no we and how dare you. How dare you?
And when I say the same thing now,
regardless of what I believe is an
actual issue that needs to be addressed
in our church, I'm saying still the
issue needs to be addressed. Let's come
together and address the issue. But no,
division is not the answer. And when I
see that that people are willing to
divide and you got to understand
beloved, we might be we we're still a
church but the the division is happening
on a micro level because people are
splitting friendships. You know, you
know how many friends I've lost that I
don't even know I've lost yet? Friends
who I've lost because because they
thought I was worshiping left Jesus.
Anytime I spoke about, you know, we got
to stand for justice. Oh, you're left
Jesus. you don't believe that that you
know that that this is wrong or this is
wrong. And I'm like, when did I ever say
that? I don't believe this is wrong.
This is wrong. No, I it was just you're
left Jesus. You're right, Jesus. And so
this division happening on this micro
level is people cutting people off. I
don't talk with them no more. Why? Cuz
she's left Jesus. He's left Jesus. He's
right Jesus. She's right Jesus. And
people just stop talking. Sometimes you
don't even know that you've been
unfriended till you're running through
your Facebook one day and you're like,
"Wait a minute. We were not friend."
The division is happening on a micro
level revealing that we are just like
the